I'm going to show you something but I'm going
to speak softly because chevas is nearby.
Today is the fiftyth day and a main factor of e
decision is not the money is the idea is on?
I wasn't getting it or having any idea.
Because the problem with chevas,
there is running,
sleeping poorly,
there is a problem with truffles,
there is a problem with the pix.
There's a lot of things going on there and then
I had to unwind to do the lecture,
you know and it gave a good bora what do you do after that?
Good thing I don't have a trunk manual.
He's even half lost in what he's going to do.
The hour cannon. Here.
You have some money.
Now set up a little business bro I need to think that I'm going
to set up a business so later the business doesn't work out.
And then Marcelo stayed in that car where he regulates.
It's just that something is really missing.
Didn't snag bro
nothing wrong with picking up uncle,
in fact there are a lot of pieces missing that mysteriously disappeared
before it's on and now we're running after it.
And what is a Chevette like?
Eighty-six hunting Cara isn't that simple,
you know?
1 question damn it's not possible that this
car doesn't pick up the parts gone bro.
There's a lot missing from the car.
We're not getting close either,
so you have to be patient.
Thank you but don't linger.
I don't want to abuse the bro guys.
The guys are being really good people with me I'm using the guys space
for free taking a shower sleeping I'm taking care of my car.
It's called crazy.
But honestly I need to find 1 space for me too Guy I'm not
able to have 1 good diet that I think affects too much.
I was thinking of investing a little of the money on a personal side.
I'll eat well and then I can think better Dude.
And I'm sure my productivity will increase so
that I can think better at this stage.
Now to think of something to put together.
My business is on so that's it bro?
If you go where you come from,
you have a tip of somewhere that I can rent cheap,
you know 1 room,
even give me a tip,
.
I'll stay with you until tomorrow.
Ouh ouh
Make you wanna Cry Baby to the hotel.